tinyit.cc 2014-11-23

# Tinyit.cc - Privacy Policy

The information we collect from you is only for the purpose of use of the member services. This information is limited to e-mail address and other important information only. You will always be fully informed to why you are giving over such information.

**2\. Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for two primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.

Tinyit.cc will never disclose your personal information to anybody except and only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Tinyit.cc; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Tinyit.cc, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Tinyit.cc, its Web site, or the public.

**3\. Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Tinyit.cc will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

**4\. Security of your Personal Information**  
Tinyit.cc strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Tinyit.cc, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located. You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

**5\. Use of Cookies**  
Cookies can be placed on your computer by Tinyit.cc for storing your preferences and login information only.
